india365.org 2012-10-17

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

At india365.org we always wanted to have a clean [privacy policy](http://www.india365.org/privacy/ "privacy policy") to protect your privacy. This page discloses the way we gather information and dissemination practices. Do let me know if you have if you  have any questions or suggestions for us.

**Personal Information**

The information you enter on this website will not be misused at any circumstances. However, we may disclose some or all the information (after taking your permission) to the third party vendors to provide information or to offer you services based on your request.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you request for information or to place an order.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.india365.org/privacy/ "privacy policy")..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site (few affiliate links included) for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. You should carefully checkout the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Stats:**

We uses Analytics software called Google analytics powered by Google for the purpose of statistics only. Analytics collects IP address, browser, screen resolution, operating system etc. The information collected is strictly not shared to any third party.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and the changes will take effect instantly.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [contact](http://www.india365.org/contact/ "contact") us using the information below.

mn.vamsi@gmail.com

Rating: 0.0/ **10** (0 votes cast)
